# **Sean Pharris**

Address: 2560 Stoneridge Drive Email: sean.pharris@colorado.edu

Colorado Springs, CO, 80919 **Phone:** (719) 322-5583

Recent University of Colorado at Boulder graduate. Motivated and reliable worker with over eight years of diverse work experience. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction, and driving business and operational goals. I have served in numerous leadership roles within various organizations, I am a conscientious, cogent, and highly organized worker with articulate communication skills and strong attention to detail. Dedicated, responsible, eager to learn, and seeking to further expand professional background.

# **Education**

## Bachelor of Arts: Psychology (8/2015 - 8/2021): University of Colorado at Boulder

Minor in Philosophy

- Involvement Collaborated on research papers, CU Hiking Club (CUHC), and Night Ride.
- Proficient Microsoft 365, G suite, scribing, and technical writing skills. Intermediate R & Python

## Boy Scouts of America: Awarded Eagle Scout (3/2015)

• Project Manager & Mentor

# **Professional Experience**

Optometric Assistant (12/2020 - 1/2022): Mountain Shadows Vision Center, Colorado Springs, CO Collaborate with medical and administrative personnel to maintain a patient-focused, engaging, and compassionate environment that improves customer satisfaction and grows diverse customer base. Focused on improving customer experience including, thoroughly explaining procedures, medications, and care plans that reduce patient anxiety and increase cooperation. Business focused responsibilities include optical sales and marketing, performing quarterly inventory records and training new staff on procedures and policies. Lead efforts to address patient concerns, inquiries, appointment requests, and billing questions. Additional responsibilities include set up and operation of technical medical equipment and implementation of care and efficiency improvements to support and enhance office operations.

# Delivery Associate (9/2020 - 12/2020): Amazon, CO

Performed on-time deliveries in fast paced environment utilizing efficient routes and GPS technology. Participated in company safety culture including daily vehicle inspections, maintaining load security, safe driving, and consistent situation awareness to avoid safety risks and company liability. Reviewed routes and expected delivery time frames to determine order of deliveries. Responsible for effective communication with dispatch to relay delays, receive route instructions, and adjust plans to meet daily targets.

### Driver (8/2019 - 9/2020): Uber / Uber Eats, Boulder & Greater Denver Metro, CO

Provided engaging and customer service focused ride services in order to achieve top customer ratings. Maintained consistent situational awareness to meet promised delivery/arrival times, spot and avoid traffic delays, and ensure safety. Kept and studied detailed mileage and fuel reports to track overall fuel costs.

### Optometric Technician (5/2016 - 9/2018): Hero Practice Services, Longmont, CO

Greeted patients, prepared exam rooms, and completed required medical/program reports. Maintained medical records system including program filing system and EHR - following clinic standard operating procedures to keep office running efficiently and effectively. Conducted patient flow, obtained medical history and visual pretesting. Performed clerical duties, such as managing the front desk, scheduling, word processing, data entry, reviewed records, answering phones, collecting/filling payments, and insurance information.

References available upon request